Register of the United States National Student Association International Commission records
Hoover Institution Archives
- PROJECTS FILE, 1946-1963
  - Cuban exchange, "Operation Friendship"
    - Correspondence, 1959-1960
    - Applicants, 1959-1960
    - Participants, 1959-1960
    - Evaluations
    - Finances, 1959
  - "Culturale" (Newsletter portraying the cultural lives of the American college students), 1947-1948
  - Cultural exchange, second annual, 1965
  - Cultural teams abroad, 1955-1956
  - Dean's Committee on NSA, 1953
  - Delegations, 1960-1963
  - Desegregation, 1956
  - Desegregation, 1957-1960 (Box 94)
  - Disarmament, 1956-1961 (Box 95)
  - Displaced university students to U.S., 1948-1951 (Box 96)
  - Dutch relief, 1953
  - East Coast Regional Conference, 1962 February 23-25
  - East European Area tours, 1954
  - Eastern European Commission, 1957
  - Editor's Exchange Program, 1957-1958
  - Editor's Exchange Program, 1957-1960 (Box 97)
  - Education (general), 1950, 1957-1958
  - Education, (general), 1958-1961 (Box 98)
  - Education (illiteracy), 1957-1958
  - Educational assistance to underdeveloped areas, 1956
  - Egyptian Town Hall Mission, Egypt, Mississippi, 1951
  - European International Student Relation Seminar, 1963
  - Evaluation, Higher, 1949-1950
  - Evaluation of NSA Deans of Women, 1953
  - Federal aid to education, 1957-1962 (Box 99)
  - Federation of African Students Studying in France, 1960-1962
  - Financing higher education, 1956-1957
  - Foreign national days in Latin American Countries, 1955-1956
  - Foreign scholarship board representative, 1955
  - Foreign student contacts, 1961
  - Foreign student exhange, 1956-1957
  - Foreign student hospitality, 1954-1961
  - Foreign student jobs, 1955-1956 (Box 100)
  - Foreign Student Leadership Project, 1957-1961
  - Foreign student orientation, 1947-1952
  - Foreign student projects
    - Young Adult Council, 1961-1962
    - Committee of Youth Organizations, 1961-1962
  - Foreign student programming on American campuses, 1961-1964
  - Foreign student scholarships, 1954-1955
  - Foreign Student Summer Project, 1952
  - Foreign student tours, 1948-1949, 1961-1962
  - Foreign Student Volunteer Service Program, 1966 (Box 101)
  - Foreign students abroad, 1955-1956
  - Foreign students in U.S.
  - Foreign tour delegation, 1963
  - French student tour, 1954
  - French North Africa (HIACOM), 1950-1951
  - Freshmen orientation, 4th Annual Conference, 1951
  - Friendship train to get relief food, 1948-1949
  - Fulbright Seminar, 1957-1958
  - Fulbright scholars, recommended list
  - General contacts, 1960-1961
  - German education, 1952
  - German Educational Research Project, 1949
  - German exchange, 1952-1954 (Box 102)
  - Governmental contracts, 1960-1961
  - Harvard-Delhi Project, 1955-1956
  - Harvard International Activities Committee, 1950-1953
  - House Un-American Activities Committee, 1960-1961
  - Human Relations Institute, 1949
  - Immigration, McCarran-Walter Act, 1952
  - India, Pakistan, Ceylon student exchange, 1953, 1958
  - India student exchange, 1951-1954
  - India student magazine, 1957
  - Indonesia, 1952, 1954
  - Indonesia student tour, 1954-1955
  - Industrial exchange, 1958
  - Interchange of information and ideas, 1948-1951
  - Internal Security Act Study, 1955
  - International Activities Directory, 1951
  - International Academic Calendar, 1957
  - International Association Exchange of Students for Technical Experience, 1950-1951, 1955-1957
  - International Awareness Project, 1948-1951 (Box 103)
  - International Evaluating Committe, 1949-1950
  - International Jobs for Americans, 1955-1956
  - International Leadership Project, 1953
  - International News Center, Georgia Tech, Atlanta, 1951-1952 (Box 104)
  - International Representation, 1954-1956
  - International Student Information Service, 1950-1954
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1954-1956 (Box 105)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1956-1957 (Box 106)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1958 (Box 107)
  - International Student Relations Seminar, 1958-1959 (Box 108)
  - International Student Relations Seminar, 1960 (Boxes 109-111)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1961 (Boxes 112-114)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1962 (Boxes 115-117)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1962-1963 (Box 118)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1963 (Boxes 119-120)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1961 (Box 316)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1964 (Boxes 121-122)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1964 (Boxes 316-318)
  - International Student Relations Seminars, 1965-1966 (Box 123)
  - International Student Relations Regional Seminars, 1956-1960
    - General
    - News clippings, 1956-1958
    - Director's evaluations, 1957-1958
    - General correspondence, 1958-1960
    - Completed projects, 1959-1960
    - General Report, 1955-1956 (Box 124)
  - International Student Relations, regional correspondence and reports
    - California, Nevada, Hawaii, 1957-1958
    - New England, 1958, 1961
    - New York City, 1957, 1963
    - Great Northwest, 1957-1958
    - Ohio and Indiana, 1957-1958
    - Pennsylvania and West Virginia, 1957
    - Rocky Mountains, 1957-1958
    - Tennessee and Kentucky, 1957-1958
    - Utah, 1958 (Box 125)
    - Illinois and Wisconsin, 1957
    - Carolinas (North and South) and Virginia, 1957
    - Iowa and Nebraska, 1957-1958
    - Mason-Dixon, 1958
    - Minnesota and Dakotas (North and South), 1957-1958
    - Missouri and Kansas, 1958
    - Michigan, 1957-1958
  - International Student Seminar I on Student Self-government and Self-help, 1950
  - International Student Seminar II on Student Self-government and Self-help, 1951 (Box 126)
  - International Student Seminar III on Student Self-government and Self-help, 1952
  - International Student Seminar IV on Student Self-government and Self-help, 1953
  - International Student Visitor's Service, 1964-1965 (Box 127)
  - International Summer University, 1955
  - International team
    - Applications, 1947
    - Correspondence, 1950
    - Correspondence, 1950-51
    - Finances, 1950
    - Preliminary report, 1950
    - Summary report, 1950
    - Miscellaneous
  - International Youth Service Abroad, circa 1961 (Box 128)
  - International Union of Students, historical background material, 1956-58
  - International Union of Students "History of U.S.N.S.A. relations with the IUS" by Peter T. Jones, 1945-1956
  - Israel tour, 1955-1956
  - Japan Seminar, 1950-1952
  - Japan-American Student Conference, 1953-1954
  - Jazz teams, 1956-1957 (Box 129)
  - Korean aid, 1954
  - Korean delegation, 1960
  - Latin American Conference, Rio, 1952
  - Latin American corespondence, 1947-1956
  - Latin American exchange, 1957-1960
  - Latin American team, applications, 1950-1951
  - Latin American team, 1955-1957
  - Latin American team, report, 1951
  - Latin American tour (Box 130)
  - Latin American Youth Congress, 1959-1960
  - Leadership training program, 1948-1952
  - Leadership development program, 1966
  - Legislative activity, 1948-1960
  - McCarran Act, 1954-1955 (Box 131)
  - Malan protest (Daniel F. Malan), abolishment of the non-segregation of races in two South African universities, 1953-1954
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Foreign Student Summer Project, III, 1950
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Foreign Student Summer Project, IV, 1951
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Foreign Student Summer Project, V, 1952
  - Michigan Daily, 1956-1957
  - Middle East, 1954-1956
  - Middle East, William R. Polk report, 1950-1951 (Box 132)
  - Middle East team, 1956-1957
  - Middle Easterners to NSA Congress, 1952
  - Middle East and Africa, 1951-1952
  - Moscow Exhibition (U.S.), Sokolniki Park, 1959 June-September (Box 133)
  - National Leadership Training Program, 1952-1953
  - National Recreation Program, 1961
  - News releases, 1950
  - Nuclear testing, circa 1962
  - Office integration, 1956
  - Okinawa report, 1957-1958
  - One Party States Conference, 1965
  - Organization Committee, 1949-1950
  - Overseas Commissioners (proposed), 1958-1959
  - Overseas publicity, 1955-1957
  - Overseas Scholarship Programs, 1955-1956
  - Panama reports, 1958-1961 (Box 134)
  - Paraguayan delegation, 1960-1961
  - Peace Corps, 1960-1961
    - Articles on Congressional records and reports, 1960-1961
    - Correspondence to and from International Commission office, 1960-1961
    - Colorado study, 1960-1961
    - Information Kit and Orientation information, 1960-1961
    - Private Aid to Education, 1960-1961
    - Statements, studies reports by individuals, organizations, and schools, 1960-1961
  - Philadelphia contacts, 1960-1961 (Box 135)
  - Planning a job opportunities conference, 1948-1949
  - Polish Exchange Program, 1958-1961
  - Polish Exchange Program, 1960-1961 (Box 136)
  - Polish tour, 1956-1957
  - Political Background Project, 1964-1965
  - Private aids to education, 1957-1960
  - Promoting newspapers, 1958
  - Public relations, 1955
  - Publications program, 1954
  - Publication series, circa 1958
  - Puerto Rico, 1948
  - Purchase card system, 1949
  - Research congress mandates (Cuban arms shipments), 1959 (Box 137)
  - Radio tapes and motion pictures, 1957-1958, 1960-1961
  - Reed College, 1965
  - Relief, 1947-1949
  - Research and Information Commission team, U.S. delegation, 1961-1963
  - Reyes (Luis A.) U.S. visit from Chile
  - Reserve Forces Act, 1955-1956
  - Returned Students Christmas Fund, 1955
  - Rocky Mountain regional conference, 1963 December 6-8
  - Saar affiliation, 1955-1956
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, I, 1947
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies II, 1948
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies III, 1949
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies IV, 1950
  - San Remo Seminar, 1954
  - Segregation, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1957-1960
  - Segregation, miscellaneous, 1956-1960 (Box 138)
  - Segregation, miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 139)
  - Sister-University project, 1964-1965
  - "Sit in" mailing, solidarity letters, 1960
  - South African Medical Scholarships Trust Fund, 1951-1952
  - South African Student Appeal, 1959-1960
  - Southeast Asia, Harvard International Activities Committee
    - General correspondence, 1951-1952
    - Advisory reports, 1952-1953
    - Australia, 1952
    - Burma, 1951-1952
    - Ceylon, 1952
    - Conant (Melvin A., Jr.) report, 1951
    - Correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box 140)
    - Ellis (William) - Correspondence, 1952-1953
    - Fisher, Frank
      - Correspondence and materials sent to, 1952
      - Reports, 1952
      - Southeast Asian trip, 1952-1953
    - Hawaii, 1952-1953 (Box 141)
    - Hong Kong, 1952-1953
    - India, 1952-1953
    - Indonesia, 1952-1953
    - Japan, 1952-1953
    - Malaya, 1952-1953
    - Mihaly (Gene) - Correspondence, 1952-1953
    - Mutual Securtiy Agency
    - Pakistan
    - Philippines
    - Pen friends requests
    - Southeast Asia Student Leader
    - Seminar, 1952
    - Team, 1952-1953
  - South Asia Tour delegation, 1963-1964
  - Southern Student Human Relations Project, 1958-1962
  - Soviet-American Scandinavian Tour, 1951-1952
  - Soviet colonialism, 1955-1956
  - Soviet exchange
    - Applications, 1963-1964
    - Applicants' correspondence, 1959-1960
    - Bogojavlensky (Sergi), correspondence, 1962 (Box 142)
    - Bugrov (E.), correspondence, 1960
    - Clippings, 1955-1960
    - Correspondence, 1954-1958
    - Correspondence and mailings, 1959-1963 (Box 143)
    - Elmanov (Boris A.) correspondence, 1962-1963
    - United States exchangees correspondence, 1955-1956
    - Gray correspondence, 1955-1956
    - Lebedev (Sergi) correspondence, 1961-1962
    - Printed materials
    - Questionnaires, 1955-1956
  - Special events kits (Box 144)
  - Speech material, 1956-1961
  - Sports festival, 1956-1957
  - Stanford University, 1966
  - Student Activities Research Study, 1955-1956
  - Student Bill of Rights, 1949-1952
  - Student Editorial Affairs Conference, 1958-1960
  - Student Exchange Algerian Scholarships, 1960-1961
  - Student Exchange Subcommission, 1954-1955
  - Student exchange
    - Campus programs, 1955-1961
    - Correspondence and miscellaneous, 1946-1959
    - Fulbright law, 1948-1949 (Box 145)
    - Germany, 1954-1955
    - Japan, 1955-1956
    - Latin America, 1955-1956
    - Putney Conference, 1954-1955
    - Refugee scholars, 1955-1956
    - Soviet, 1953-1955
    - U.S. State Department, 1954-1955
    - Valway (Henry L.) case, 1948
    - Workcamp at Sakiet, 1959-1960
  - Student Government Information Service, 1955-1956 (Box 146)
  - Student Government Survey, Ford Foundation, 1954-1955
  - Student health, 1955-1956
  - Student housing in U.S., 1951-1952
  - Student leader fellowships, 1952
  - Student leader scholarships, 1954
  - Student Leadership Training Seminar, 1964
  - Student Mutual Assistance Program, 1950-1952
  - Student Mutual Assistance Program, library, 1950-1953
  - Student Mutual Assistance Program, West Africa, 1950-1951
  - Student News Service, 1950-1951
  - Student Project for International Responsibility, 1960-1967
  - Student Project for International Responsibility, 1960-1967 (Boxes 147-148)
  - Student Ship Project, 1947-1948 (Box 149)
  - Student travel in U.S., 1954-1955
  - Study abroad, 1955-1957
  - Symposium on Russia, 1958-1959
  - Subcommission on Student Unions, 1955-1956
  - Summary of International Commission activities, 1958
  - Summer hospitality, 1946-1948
  - Summer jobs, 1965-1966
  - Technical Assistance to National Union of Students, 1957-1961
  - Technical Assistance to World University Service, 1960-1961
  - Technical Team Southeast Asia, 1953-1954
  - Textbooks, 1956-1957
  - Touchet (Francis) incident, 1952
  - Tour of New England non-member schools, 1954
  - Travel itineraries for foreign students, 1960-1962
  - Travel pool, 1946-1948
  - Tunisian delegation, 1960-1961
  - Underdeveloped Areas Conference, 1951 March 2-4
  - Union Generale des Etudiants d'Afrique Occidentale, 1960-1961
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics and U.S. relations, 1946-1947
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics youth editors' visit to the U.S., 1958 May 17-June 16
  - United Nations Day Programs, 1953-1955
  - United Nations Day Programs, 1955-1963 (Box 150)
  - United Nations disarmament, 1960
  - United States State Department, temporary disarmament, 1960
  - United States education, articles on for circulation abroad, 1957
  - United States Information Agency, 1955-1956
  - United States National Student Association
    - Proposed NSA emblem pins, 1960-1961
    - Sports affairs, 1964-1965
    - Communism, 1956
    - Confederation of National Students, Mexico, work camp, 1963
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, exchange, 1959-1960
  - Unity Seminar
  - Universal Student Cooperation and Student Unity
  - University reform, 1965, 1967
  - Visiting team of Architectural Students, 1958-1959
  - Vocational Guidance Subcommission, 1949-1950
  - West meets East
  - White House Conference, 1955-1956
  - Williamsburg, 1955
  - World Assembly of Youth, Singapore Conference, 1954
  - World Refugee Year, 1959-1960
  - World Student News distribution, 1947
  - World University Service, experiment, 1957-1958
  - World University Service, General Assembly, 1954
  - World University Service, Indian seminar, 1953
  - World Youth Forum, 1960-1961
  - World Youth Forum, 1960-1961 (Box 151)
  - Yale-American Studies for Foreign Students, 1948-1949
  - Young Adult Council team to North Africa, 1958-1959
  - Young Adult Council team to Soviet Union, 1958-1959
  - Young Adult Council and World Assembly of Youth, Relegation, 1960
  - Youth Corps, Point Four
  - Youth Council, 1963
  - Youth March, Washington D.C., 1959 April 18
  - Yugoslavia, 1950-1951
  - Yugoslavian Exchange, 1952-1953
- NATIONAL UNIONS OF STUDENTS FILE, 1947-1966
  Correspondence, reports, minutes of meetings, notes, and lists, relating to National Unions of Students in various countries, arranged in two subseries--one by type of document and the second by geographical location.
  - General file (Box 152)
    - History of National Union of Students, (2 copies), 1960
    - Address lists
    - List of officers, 1960
    - Office memoranda, circa 1957
  - Geographical file
    - Aden, 1962, 1965
    - Afghanistan, 1959-1965
    - Africa
      - Correspondence, 1948-1955
      - Correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 153)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 154)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1967 (Box 155)
    - Africa below the Sahara, 1965-1966
    - Africa, confidential files, index, 1965-1967
    - Africa, Conferences on, 1965-1967
    - Africa, delegations to, 1962-1967 (Box 156)
    - Africa, education in, circa 1962
    - Africa operation crossroads in, 1966-1967
    - Africa, printed material, 1966-1967
    - Africa, reports, 1966-1967
    - African headership Seminars, circa 1964
    - African Student Affairs, bibliography, circa 1964
    - African students in U.S., 1961
    - Albania, 1961-1966
    - Algeria
      - Correspondence, 1955-1960
      - Clippings and reports, 1957-1958 (Box 157)
      - Clippings and reports, 1958-1960 (Box 158)
      - Clippings and reports, 1960-1961 (Box 159)
      - Publications, 1960-1961
      - Union generale des etudiants musulmans algeriens, 1962-1965 (Box 160)
    - Angola
      - Correspondence, 1960-1967
      - Correspondence about film, "Angola: Journey to a War, ", 1962 (Box 161)
      - Clippings, 1961-1962
      - Scholarships, 1966-1967
      - Solidarity day, 1961 March 15 - 1964
    - Angolan student, 1962-1963
    - Angolan student groups, 1963 (Box 162)
    - Angola (UNEA) Union of National Students of Angola, 1962-1964
    - Angola (UGEAN) Union of Students North Africa, 1962-1964
    - Arab-Israeli Conflict Seminar, 1965 October (Box 163)
    - Arab Student Leadership Program, 1965-1966
    - Arabia, 1958-1960
    - Argentina, 1956-1967 (Boxes 163-165)
    - Asia, 1946-1959 (Box 165)
    - Asia, 1959-1964 (Box 166)
    - Asia-African Student Conference, 1956-1957
    - Austria, 1946-1958
    - Austria, 1958-1965 (Box 167)
    - Australia, 1946-1957
    - Australia, 1957-1963 (Box 168)
    - Australia, National Union of Australian University Students, 1963-1964 (Box 169)
    - Baltic Students in Exile, 1950-1951
    - Burundi, 1962-1963
    - Basutoland, 1960-1965
    - Bechuanaland, 1962-1965
    - Belgium, 1948-1965
    - Belgian Congo, 1955-1959 (Box 170)
    - Bhutan, 1960
    - Bolivia, 1952-1959
    - Bolivia, 1960-1967
    - "Bolivian Left," by Hugo Specter
    - Bolivia, San Simeon University, revolutionary manifesto
    - Brazil, 1946-1962 (Box 171)
    - Brazil, 1962-1967 (Box 172)
    - Brazil, National Union of Students of Brazil, 1961-1962
    - Britain, 1946-1966 (Box 173)
    - Britain, 1957-1961 (Box 174)
    - Britain, NUS Executive and Council minutes, 1949-1965 (Box 175)
    - Britain, publications, 1948-1950
    - Britain, National Union of Students of England, Wales and Northern Ireland, 1963-1964
    - British students visit the Soviet Union
    - British Guiana, 1962-1964
    - British West Indies, 1962-1963
    - Bulgaria, 1946-1966
    - Burma, 1948-1956
    - Burma, 1956-1963 (Box 176)
    - Burundi, 1963-1964
    - Cambodia, 1955-1964
    - Cameroons, 1958-1965
    - Canada, 1946-1953 (Box 177)
    - Canada, 1953-1960 (Box 178)
    - Canada, 1960-1966 (Box 179)
    - Canada, 1960-1966 (Box 318)
    - Canada, clippings and reports, 1955-1963 (Box 180)
    - Canada, clippings and reports, 1964-1965 (Box 181)
    - Canada, National Federation of Canadian University Students, 1955-1960
    - Canada, National Federation of Canadian University Students, 1959-1964 (Box 182)
    - Canada, publications, 1955-1956, 1960-1961
    - Canada, student summer employment, circa 1963
    - Central African Republic, 1960-1963 (Box 183)
    - Central America, 1955-1965
    - Central America, education, integration, 1962
    - Ceylon, 1952-1964
    - Chad, 1960
    - Chile, 1948-1960
    - Chile, 1960-1967 (Box 184)
    - Chile, Federation of Students of Chile, 1960-1961
    - Chile, Union of Federations Universities of Chile, 1960-1964
    - China, 1949-1964 (Box 185)
    - China (Taiwan), 1960-1961 (Box 186)
    - China, Peoples Republic of China and all China Student Federation (Communist), 1962-1964
    - Colombia, 1946-1963
    - Colombia, 1963-1967 (Box 187)
    - Colombia, Confederation of Students, Universities of Colombia, 1962
    - Columbia, Council of Students Columbia University, 1960, 1962
    - Congo, 1959-1961
    - Congo, 1961-1967 (Box 188)
    - Costa Rica, 1961-1967
    - Costa Rica, Federation of Students of Universities of Costa Rica, 1962-1965
    - Cuba, 1947-1960 (Box 189)
    - Cuba, 1960-1963 (Box 190)
    - Cuba, Director Revolution of Students, 1961-1964 (Box 191)
    - Cuba, Federation of University Students, 1960-1964 (Box 192)
    - Cuba, Front Democratic Revolution (Cuba Front), 1960-1961
    - Cuba, Exiled Cuban students in Santo Domingo, 1963
    - Cyprus, 1956-1965
    - Czechoslovakia (in exile), 1948-1957 (Box 193)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1945-1967
    - Dahomey, 1962-1967 (Box 194)
    - Denmark, 1947-1965
    - Dominican Republic, 1949-1964
    - Dominican Republic, 1960-1965 (Box 195)
    - East Africa, 1959-1967 (Box 196)
    - East African Students Union, 1966-1967
    - East Germany, 1955-1965
    - Ecuador, 1947-1967
    - Egypt, 1947-1962 (Box 197)
    - El Salvador, 1957-1966
    - England, Wales and Northern Ireland, 1955-1965
    - Estonia, 1951-1955
    - Ethiopia, 1957-1967
    - Europe (general), 1950-1966 (Box 198)
    - Finland, 1947-1964
    - Formosa, 1955-1962
    - France, Association generale, Students of Reims, 15th Congress, 1962 (Box 199)
    - France, correspondence and memoranda, 1946-1955
    - France, correspondence and memoranda, 1955-1960 (Box 200)
    - France, correspondence and memoranda, 1960-1965 (Box 201)
    - France, reports and clippings, 1957-1962
    - France, student publications, 1955-1957 (Box 202)
    - France, student publications, 1957-1963 (Box 203)
    - France, Union of National Students of France, correspondence, 1960-1964
    - France, Union of National Students of France, general, 1963-1964 (Box 204)
    - France, Union of National Students of France, working papers, 1954-1955
    - French West Africa, lst Congress of African Students, 1960
    - French West Indies, 1960-1961, 1964
    - Gambia, 1961-1966
    - Germany, correspondence and memoranda, 1947-1955 (Box 205)
    - Germany, correspondence and memoranda, 1955-1966 (Box 206)
    - Germany, clippings and reports, 1957-1958
    - Germany clippings and reports, 1959-1960 (Box 207)
    - Germany, student publications, 1954-1963 (Box 208)
    - Germany, Greifswald University Affair, 1954-1956
    - Ghana, 1957-1967
    - Goa, 1957 (Box 209)
    - Gold Coast, 1953-1957
    - Great Britain, 1961-1963
    - Greece, 1947-1965
    - Guadalupe, 1963
    - Guayaquil, 1961-1962
    - Guinea, 1961-1964
    - Guyana, 1964-1966
    - Guatemala, 1947-1960
    - Guatemala, 1960-1966 (Box 210)
    - Haiti, 1960-1966
    - Honduras, 1947-1966
    - Hong Kong, 1950-1964 (Box 211)
    - Hungary, American Hungarian Student Association, 1956-1957
    - Hungary, American Hungarian Students in the U.S., 1957-1958
    - Hungary, Ralph Della Cava correspondence, 1957
    - Hungary, Istavan Laszlo correspondence, 1956-1957
    - Hungary, correspondence, 1947-1957 (Box 212)
    - Hungary, correspondence, 1957-1965 (Box 213)
    - Hungary, clippings and reports, 1957-1962 (Box 214)
    - Hungary, Coordinating Committee, 1956-1957
    - Hungary, fund raising, 1957-1958 (Box 215)
    - Hungary, brief history of the Hungarian uprising, 1956
    - Hungary, Hungarian Revolution data, 1957